<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Faviorite Place</string>
    <string name="saint_martin">St. Martins Island (Bengali: সেন্ট মার্টিন্স দ্বীপ) is a small island (area only 8 km2) in the northeastern part of the Bay of Bengal, about 9 km south of the tip of the Coxs Bazar-Teknaf peninsula, and forming the southernmost part of Bangladesh. There is a small adjoining island that is separated at high tide, called Chera Dwip. It is about 8 kilometres (5 miles) west of the northwest coast of Myanmar, at the mouth of the Naf River.</string>
    <string name="sajekvalley">Sajek Valley is an emerging tourist spot in Bangladesh situated among the hills of Kasalong range of mountains in Sajek union, Baghaichhari Upazila in Rangamati District.[1] The valley is 1800 feet above sea level.[2] Sajek valley is known as the Queen of Hills and Roof of Rangamati.</string>
    <string name="nilgiri">Nilgiri resorts is one of the most popular and beautiful resorts in Bangladesh, It is situated on the hill side in Bandarban District, Surrounded by beautiful hilly natural views and clouds most of the time. An esthetic place for enjoying serenity with ultimate relaxation away from city boredom. You find here various tYou will find yourself in the embrace of the clouds.</string>
    <string name="coxbazar">Coxs Bazar  is a city, fishing port, tourism centre and district headquarters in southeastern Bangladesh. The beach in Coxs Bazar is sandy and has a gentle slope; with an unbroken length of 120 km (75 mi), it is the longest natural sea beach in the world.[2][3][4] It is located 150 km (93 mi) south of the divisional headquarter of Chittagong. Coxs Bazar is also known by the name Panowa, which translates literally as "yellow flower". Another old name was "Palongkee".

The modern Coxs Bazar derives its name from Captain Hiram Cox, an officer of the British East India Company. Cox was appointed Superintendent of Palongkee outpost after Warren Hastings became Governor of Bengal. He embarked upon the task of rehabilitation and settlement of the Arakanese refugees in the area.[5] Captain Cox died in 1799 before he could finish his work. To commemorate his role in rehabilitation work, a market was established and named Cox's Bazar after him. Unlike many locations in the Indian Subcontinent where place names dating from the colonial period have been changed, Cox's name is still retained in the city he founded.</string>

</resources>
